http://www.prostatcorp.com/legal/privacy-statement.asp

Privacy Statement
Prostat Corporation is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of the prostatcorp.com site (the "Site"); it does not apply to other online or offline Prostat Corporation sites, products or services. By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you to provide a service or carry out a transaction that you have requested such as receiving information about Prostat Corporation products and services, entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site or service, signing up for an event or training, or when purchasing, downloading and/or registering Prostat Corporation products. The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name, work e-mail, work phone, work address, information about your job function, information about your company, and credit card information.
The Site may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used to help improve the site, analyze trends and administer the site.
Prostat Corporation technical communities provide opportunities to interact with Prostat Corporation employees, experts, and your peers in order to share knowledge and news about Prostat Corporation products and related technologies.
Use of
your Personal Information
The personal information collected on this Site will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized.
In support of these uses, Prostat Corporation may use personal information to provide you with more effective customer service, to improve the Site and any related Prostat Corporation products or services, and to make the Site easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Site to your particular preference or interests. In order to offer you a more consistent experience in your interactions with Prostat Corporation, information collected by prostatcorp.com may be combined with information collected by other Prostat Corporation services.
We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including critical updates and notifications. Additionally, with your permission, we may send you information about other Prostat Corporation products and services, and/or share information with Prostat Corporation partners so they may send you information about their products and services.
When you sign up for a newsletter or agree to receive promotional e-mail, prostatcorp.com may use customized links or similar technologies to track e-mail links that you click. We may associate that information with your personal information in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or purchase information. Each e-mail communication includes an unsubscribe link allowing you to stop delivery of that type of communication.
Some services on prostatcorp.com offer individuals the ability to publicly display certain personal information, such as for a Prostat Corporation partner who wishes to publish contact information as part of offering a business service. Participation in such services is always optional.
Prostat Corporation occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as Web site hosting, packaging, mailing and delivering prizes, answering customer questions about products and services, and sending information about our products, special offers, and other services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
Prostat Corporation may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Prostat Corporation or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Prostat Corporation and our family of Web sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Prostat Corporation employees or agents, users of Prostat Corporation products or services, or members of the public.
Personal information collected on the Site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Prostat Corporation or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Prostat Corporation abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.
Control of your Personal Information
Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the Site will not be shared outside of Prostat Corporation and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission. As described below in the next section, you can access your personal information and make choices about how you wish to be contacted.
Please be aware that this privacy statement and any choices you make on the Site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to Prostat Corporation in the context of other, separately operated, Prostat Corporation products or services.
Prostatcorp.com may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service or security issues related to a product or service you requested, or confirming you requested a product or service. In some services offered by prostatcorp.com, contact with the customer is an intrinsic part of the service. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the service(s) you have chosen.
Use of Cookies
We use cookies on this Site to ensure the integrity of the registration process and to personalize the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases site navigation, and so on. When you return to the Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the site's features that you customized.
Web beacons, also known as clear gif technology, or action tags, may be used to assist in delivering the cookie on our site. This technology is a tool we use to compile aggregated statistics about prostatcorp.com Web site usage, such as how many visitors clicked on key elements (such as links or graphics) on a prostatcorp.com Web page, blog or a newsletter. We may share aggregated site statistics with partner companies.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other Web sites you visit.
Enforcement of this Privacy Statement
If you have questions regarding this statement, you should contact prostatcorp.com. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry, or if your inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe through the TRUSTe Dispute Resolution Process at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php. TRUSTe will serve as a liaison with this Web site to resolve your concerns.
Changes to this Statement
We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our Web site or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.
Contact Information
Prostat Corporation welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that Prostat Corporation has not adhered to this privacy statement, please contact us electronically or via postal mail at the address provided below, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Prostatcorp.com privacy
Prostat Corporation
399 Wall Street, Suite G
Glendale Heights, IL 60139 US
Last Updated: April 1, 2005
Privacy Statement
Warranty Information
Feedback
©2020 Prostat Corporation. All rights reserved.
